EZEQUIEL CASTELLANDS

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



ezecastellanos.com.ar





+54 9 387 5432979



Salta, Argentina



github.com/EzequielCaste

TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML5, CSS and JavaScript
- React.js, Next.js
- Sass, Tailwind CSS
- Node.js, MongoDB, Express
- Git and GitHub

PROJECTS

React Movie App

https://cmyk-tiger.netlify.app/

- Shows movie recommendations fetching data from the TheMovieDB.org API
- Group project which helped us implement version control with Git and GitHub
- Developed with React, React Router and Material UI

Portfolio Website

http://ezecastellanos.com.ar

- Built using Next.js and Tailwind
- Responsive design for small and large screens

ABOUT ME

Front-End developer and English/Spanish translator with previous experience working in group projects for open-source IT communities. I enjoy creating applications and websites that are accessible and interactive. I aim to learn and improve my skills on the latest web technologies and challenge myself every day to learn something new and become a more effective developer.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

AO COPIERS | Dec. 2020 - Apr. 2021

- Maintain and improve company website
- Implementing responsive design for mobile

Volunteer Translator

FREECODECAMP | Feb. 2021 - Present

- Translation of technical articles
- Proofreading and correction of articles

Senior Translator & Office Assistant

TORRE-PULISICH ACCOUNTING FIRM | Aug. 2014 - Present

- Translation of Accounting Reports, Board Meeting Minutes, Bylaws and Audit Reports
- Translation of emails and conference calls
- Preparation of Payment Orders and Checks

EDUCATION & TRAINING

freeCodeCamp

Mar. 2019 - Mar. 2020

Completed 5 Certifications:

- Responsive Web Design (300 hours)
- Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures (300 hours)
- Front End Libraries (300 hours)
- Data Visualization (300 hours)
- APIs and Microservices (300 hours)

Udemy

Jun. 2020 - Oct. 2020

React: From zero to expert (Hooks and MERN) by Fernando Herrera Front End Web Development Ultimate Course 2021